accelerated-ideas.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Accelerated Ideas

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us and we recognise that the privacy of your personal information must be safeguarded. This site does not collect any personal information which could be sold to another company, nor would we ever change this agreement. 

By using this site, you agree to the use of cookies and data collection, which is described below. 

### General Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser version, visitor location. None of this information can personally identify visitors to this site. The information is recorded for routine administration and also to improve the experience for visitors the next time they view the website.. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies on our site to offer you a better experience. Some of these cookies are controlled by other companies such as Google or Amazon. We always verify that the cookies on our site comply with our own privacy concerns, ensuring that your data remains private. 

_The three types of cookies we use are:_

**Google Adsense (Doubleclick cookie)**

To display relevant adverts which help to fund our site. These adverts may be targeted to your particular interests or location, to offer you a better experience. This is achieved by using cookies which record small amounts of information. This information is not personally identifiable. 

You can choose to opt out of interest based advertising by using the following link:  

For more information on DoubleClick please read:  

**Google Analytics**

This is a statistical tool that helps us understand which pages are popular on our site, which browsers are used and many other interesting statistics. This tool also uses cookies to facilitate this process, but it never records any personally identifiable information. 

If you would like to read Google’s privacy policy, please read:  
<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

**Custom cookies**

This site may use our own cookies to provide a better experience for you. A good example is a cookie which tracks if you have logged into the site, or whether you have permission to add a new comment. We never store any personal information in these cookies, they are only used to ensure the site functions correctly. 

We may choose to use other services to improve our site in the future.. 

### Disabling Cookies

You can chose to disable cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites, and will usually negatively affect your experience. 

Deleting cookies does not permanently prevent cookies from being used in the future. Unless you have settings that disable cookies, the next time you visit a site, a new cookie will be added. 

### Information we collect

To help you participate in discussions on this site, we may display some personal information. This can include your name and photo, if you choose to share either of those.. 

This is in agreement with the information you choose to disclose, when you add a new comment. It is up to you to decide if you want to use your full name, and if you’re happy for your social network photo to appear. You do not have to provide either of these if you want to remain anonymous. 

In some cases we do store your email address, for the sole purpose of providing updates, when a new comment is added to a particular discussion, or when your own comment is approved by administrators. You do not have to provide your email, and we never force you to do this before you can participate in discussions. 

You are also responsible for the text you add to your comment - whether you choose to include personal information such as an email address, name, phone number, or any other personal details. 

### Want to ask a question?

If you’re unsure about any of the information above, please contact us and we will be happy to help. 

Contact Us

## Share..
